[
    {
        "id": 1,
        "question": "1 - 1",
        "choices": [10, 0, 5, 6],
        "correct": 0
    },
    {
        "id": 2,
        "question": "4 - 1",
        "choices": [2, 5, 3, 4],
        "correct": 3
    },
    {
        "id": 3,
        "question": "6 - 2",
        "choices": [6, 4, 2, 3],
        "correct": 4
    },
    {
        "id": 4,
        "question": "3 - 4",
        "choices": [7, 1, 4, 5],
        "correct": 1
    },
    {
        "id": 5,
        "question": "4 - 5",
        "choices": [9, 6, 1, 2],
        "correct": 1
    },
    {
        "id": 6,
        "question": "10 - 10",
        "choices": [10, 0, 20, 25],
        "correct": 0
    },
    {
        "id": 7,
        "question": "1 - 10",
        "choices": [2, 9, 11, 3],
        "correct": 9
    },
    {
        "id": 8,
        "question": "7 - 2",
        "choices": [8, 4, 9, 5],
        "correct": 5
    },
    {
        "id": 9,
        "question": "4 - 4",
        "choices": [7, 8, 4, 5],
        "correct": 0
    },
    {
        "id": 10,
        "question": "8 - 2",
        "choices": [5, 0, 6, 3],
        "correct": 6
    }
]